( wood thumping )
( Eugeo panting )
Kirito: YOU HAVE TO THINK ABOUT
WHAT YOU’RE PUTTING
BEHIND YOUR STRIKES.
THAT’S WHAT’S GONNA TIP THINGS
IN YOUR FAVOR.
- Eugeo: WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- Kirito: IT’S LIKE,
FOR VOLO, IT’S THE PRIDE
AND RESPONSIBILITY
THAT COMES
WITH BEING FROM A FAMILY
THAT TEACHES SWORDSMANSHIP.
FOR GOLGOROSSO,
IT’S THE CONFIDENCE HE’S GOT
FROM HAVING MUSCLES OF STEEL,
AND FOR LIENA,
IT’S THE PRIDE SHE TAKES
IN HER POLISHED SKILLS.
THAT’S THE REASON
WHY THEIR ATTACKS
ARE AS POWERFUL AS THEY ARE.
Eugeo: THEN WHAT DO YOU THINK
I SHOULD PUT BEHIND MY SWORD?
Kirito: THAT’S SOMETHIN’
YOU’RE GONNA HAVE
TO FIGURE OUT YOURSELF.
Eugeo: I’M NOT A NOBLE
OR A SWORDSMAN.
ALL I HAVE ARE MY YEARS SPENT
IN THE FOREST WIELDING AN AX,
THAT AND THE AINCRAD STYLE
KIRITO TAUGHT ME.
WAIT. I HAVE SOMETHING ELSE.
♪
( grunts )
♪ SHINY SWORD, MY DIAMOND ♪
( singing in Japanese )
♪ IT’S TIME ♪
- ( wood thumping )
- ( bell tolling )
( Eugeo sighs )
Raios: IT SEEMS DISCIPLE EUGEO
PREFERS HACKING AWAY AT LOGS,
RATHER THAN WORKING
ON HIS FORM.
Humbert: I RECALL
ONCE HEARING SIR EUGEO
USED TO BE A WOODCUTTER
IN SOME BACKWOODS HOVEL.
PERHAPS THE EXTENT
OF HIS KNOWLEDGE
IS LIMITED TO METHODS
OF ATTACKING LUMBER.
Raios: HOW TRULY UNFORTUNATE.
IF THAT IS INDEED THE CASE,
THEN AS SOMEONE WHO HAPPENS
TO TRAIN IN THE SAME DORM,
PERHAPS I SHOULD
GRACIOUSLY LEND A HAND
AND INSTRUCT HIM
ON PROPER TECHNIQUE.
Humbert: MY,
WHAT A CONSIDERATE THING
OF YOU TO OFFER, LORD RAIOS.
YOU TRULY ARE
AN EXEMPLARY NOBLE.
WHAT SAY YOU TO THAT, SIR EUGEO?
WILL YOU ACCEPT
LORD RAIOS’S GENEROSITY
AND HAVE HIM TRAIN YOU?
IT’S A ONCE-IN-A-LIFETIME
OPPORTUNITY.
( Eugeo sighs )
I APPRECIATE THE OFF--( gasps )
Kirito: SOME UPPERCLASSMEN
USE THEIR STATUS
AS A SOURCE OF POWER.
Eugeo: IS THAT
WHY FIRST SEAT RAIOS
AND SECOND SEAT HUMBERT
ARE SO STRONG?
Kirito: IT’S A LITTLE DIFFERENT
WITH THOSE GUYS.
THEIR EGOS ARE
ON A WHOLE ’NOTHER LEVEL.
Eugeo: WHY DO YOU THINK THAT IS?
Kirito: ’CAUSE THEY’RE
A COUPLE OF JERKS.
HELL, THEY’VE BEEN LOOKING
DOWN THEIR NOSES AT PEOPLE
SINCE THE DAY THEY WERE BORN.
THEY SURE
DON’T THINK MUCH OF US.
FOR ONE, WE’RE FROM
OUTSIDE THE CAPITAL,
PLUS WE DON’T HAVE
ANY KIND OF NOBLE HERITAGE.
Eugeo: THIS MIGHT BE
A GOOD OPPORTUNITY
FOR ME TO FIND OUT JUST
WHAT THEIR EGOS ARE CAPABLE OF.
FORGIVE ME
FOR MISSPEAKING JUST NOW.
I WOULD HAPPILY ACCEPT
A LESSON FROM YOU.
Humbert: OH, HO!
HE CAN’T BE SERIOUS!
Eugeo: I AM.
IN FACT, I WOULD LIKE MY LESSON
IN THE FORM OF A MATCH WITH YOU,
SIR HUMBERT,
IF THAT ISN’T TOO MUCH TROUBLE.
( grunts )
( Humbert gasps )
WHY, YOU ROTTEN--
Raios: MAY I REMIND YOU
THAT LORD HUMBERT
IS NO SLOUCH
WHEN IT COMES TO SWORDPLAY.
HE MAY END UP STRIKING YOU.
Eugeo: I WOULD PREFER IF HE
STOPPED JUST SHORT OF THAT,
BUT IF HE HITS ME,
THEN I MUST ACCEPT IT.
THIS LESSON IS FOR MY BENEFIT,
AFTER ALL.
Humbert: VERY WELL.
I WILL BE MORE THAN HAPPY
TO DEMONSTRATE
MY SKILLS FOR YOU, SIR EUGEO.
LET US BEGIN THEN!
PREPARE TO BEAR WITNESS
TO THE ESSENCE
OF THE HIGH-NORKIAN STYLE!
Eugeo: LIGHTNING SLASH!
THE NORKIAN STYLE’S SECRET MOVE!
Humbert: EN GARDE! ( yells )
( Eugeo yells )
( Humbert gasping )
Raios: HUH.
Eugeo: IF IT’S A CASE
OF WHO’S STRONGER, I AM!
Humbert: DON’T GET COCKY,
YOU COMMONER!
Eugeo: HIS POWER SURGED.
IS THAT WHAT HIS ARROGANCE
IS CAPABLE OF?
Humbert: YOUR SWORD STYLE
IS A GOOD MATCH FOR YOU,
PRIMITIVE AND UNSIGHTLY.
( Eugeo grunting )
Humbert: LET’S SEE HOW YOU FARE
AFTER I CRUSH YOUR SHOULDER.
( Eugeo grunts )
I HAVE TO SWITCH SKILLS.
( Humbert gasps )
( Eugeo yells )
- ( Humber groans )
- Raios: THAT IS ENOUGH!
I DECLARE THIS MATCH A DRAW.
Humbert: BUT, LORD RAIOS!
I CAN’T WALK AWAY
FROM THIS ROGUE WITH A DRAW!
I MUST FINISH THIS!
Raios: STAND DOWN, HUMBERT.
( Humbert gasps )
( growls )
( scabbard scrapes )
Raios: FOR WHAT IT’S WORTH,
DISCIPLE EUGEO,
YOUR OUTLANDISH MOVES
WERE QUITE ENTERTAINING.
AFTER GRADUATING,
PERHAPS YOU SHOULD CONSIDER
SEEKING A CALLING
WITH THE IMPERIAL CIRCUS.
Eugeo: THANK YOU FOR
THE SUGGESTION, DISCIPLE RAIOS.
Raios: IN DUE TIME,
I WILL GIVE YOU
MY OWN DEMONSTRATION
OF A NOBLEMAN’S POW--
Eugeo: I’M FREE NOW, IF YOU ARE.
( Humbert gasps )
Raios: THERE IS MORE TO BATTLE
THAN WAVING A SWORD AROUND,
YOU NAMELESS BUFFOON.
( Eugeo sighs )
IT’S BEEN THREE DAYS.
THEY SHOULD HAVE TRIED
GETTING BACK AT ME BY NOW.
I WONDER WHY THEY HAVEN’T.
Kirito: THEY’D BE
BREAKIN’ THE RULES,
THE SCHOOL’S
AND THE TABOO INDEX’S.
THOSE DON’T MAKE IT EASY
TO HARASS PEOPLE.
ON THE OTHER HAND, ANYTHING THAT
DOESN’T FALL UNDER THE RULES
IS UP FOR DEBATE.
THEY COULD BE LOOKIN’
FOR A LOOPHOLE.
Eugeo: YOU THINK
THEY’D GO THAT FAR
JUST TO SPITE ME?
Kirito: I DON’T KNOW.
MAYBE THEY’RE NOT PLANNING
ON DOING ANYTHING.
IT’S POSSIBLE THEY’RE
JUST TRYING TO PSYCHE YOU OUT.
WHATEVER YOU DO,
DON’T LET IT GET TO YOU.
NO MATTER WHAT,
YOU GOTTA STAY COOL.
Eugeo: WHAT DID YOU SAY?
- STAY WHAT, NOW?
- Kirito: OH, UH...
THAT’S THE SECRET MANTRA
OF THE AINCRAD STYLE.
IT’S PRETTY MUCH THE SAME
AS SAYING, "STAY CALM."
YOU CAN ALSO USE IT
TO SAY GOODBYE TO SOMEONE.
IT’S LIKE ANOTHER WAY
OF SAYING, "SEE YOU LATER."
Eugeo: OH. OKAY!
I’LL REMEMBER THAT.
"STAY COOL."
WHAT AN UNUSUAL THING TO SAY.
STAY COOL? BIZARRE.
Kirito: ALL RIGHT,
I’M GONNA GO HIT THE SACK.
Eugeo: AND WHY "COOL"?
Kirito: OH, HEY,
BY THE WAY, ABOUT TOMORROW,
I HAVE TO RUN SOME ERRANDS,
SO YOU’RE ON YOUR--
Eugeo: OH, NO, YOU DON’T!
WE PROMISED TIESE AND RONIE
WE’D TAKE THEM OUT FOR A PICNIC,
AND BY "WE," I MEAN US,
SO IF YOU THINK
YOU CAN GET OUT OF IT,
YOU’RE MISTAKEN.
( Kirito sighs )
Eugeo: THEY’LL BE HERE
AT 9:00 SHARP,
SO MAKE SURE YOU’RE READY
TO LEAVE BY THEN. YOU GOT IT?
Kirito: OKAY, OKAY.
DO ME A FAVOR, THOUGH,
AND WAKE ME UP AT 8:00.
I NEED TO CATCH UP
ON SOME SLEEP.
Eugeo: NO! 8:00’S WAY TOO LATE!
MAKE IT 7:30!
AND STAY COOL.
Kirito: I KNOW I TOLD YOU
THAT PHRASE
IS LIKE SAYING, "BYE,"
BUT IT’S NOT SOMETHING YOU SAY
TO SOMEONE GOIN’ TO BED.
Eugeo: WHY NOT?
Kirito: ’CAUSE YOU DON’T.
YOU USE IT WHEN YOU’RE REALLY
SAYING GOODBYE TO SOMEONE.
Eugeo: OH.
WHAT A COMPLICATED PHRASE.
IF WHAT KIRITO SAID IS TRUE,
ARE HUMBERT AND RAIOS CAPABLE
OF SIDESTEPPING THE LAWS
OF THE AXIOM CHURCH?
( sighs ) WHAT AM I SAYING?
YOU CAN’T EVEN DOUBT
THE TABOO INDEX,
MUCH LESS DISOBEY IT.
IF THERE WERE A WAY AROUND IT,
I COULD HAVE DONE SOMETHING
INSTEAD OF STAND THERE
AND WATCH ALICE GET TAKEN AWAY.
WHY COULDN’T I DISOBEY
WHEN I HAD THE CHANCE?
♪
ALICE.
( birds chirping )
( frog chirping )
Tiese: EUGEO, ARE YOU LISTENING?
EUGEO?
Eugeo: HUH? SORRY.
I MISSED THAT LAST PART.
YOU WERE SAYING?
( Tiese sighs )
YOU DIDN’T HEAR A SINGLE WORD.
Eugeo: I’M SORRY. I JUST--
I WAS JUST ADMIRING
HOW BEAUTIFUL THE FOREST WAS.
IT HAS ANIMALS
I’VE NEVER SEEN BEFORE.
Tiese: REALLY?
Eugeo: YEAH, LIKE THAT ONE.
Tiese: OH, THAT? THAT’S JUST
A PLAIN OLD GOLDEN FLYING FOX.
DON’T TELL ME
YOU’VE NEVER SEEN ONE.
THEY’RE IN EVERY TREE
IN THE CAPITAL.
Eugeo: OH, RIGHT.
I GUESS YOU’D BE USED TO THEM,
SINCE YOU WERE BORN
AND RAISED HERE.
Tiese: THAT’S TRUE.
Eugeo: DO YOUR FOLKS
LIVE NEARBY?
Tiese: NO.
THEY LIVE IN DISTRICT EIGHT.
IT’S A BIT OF A WAYS AWAY
FROM WHERE WE ARE IN FIVE.
Eugeo: OH. YOU DON’T SAY.
UH...
HANG ON. IF I’M NOT MISTAKEN,
DON’T YOU COME
FROM A FAMILY OF NOBLES?
I THOUGHT ALL OF THE MANSIONS
WERE IN DISTRICTS
THREE AND FOUR.
Tiese: ONLY NOBLES
WHO ARE FOURTH RANK OR HIGHER
GET TO LIVE IN THAT DISTRICT.
MY FATHER IS
A SIXTH-RANK NOBLEMAN.
THEREFORE, HE HAS
NO JUDICIAL AUTHORITY.
Eugeo: I DIDN’T KNOW THAT.
I THOUGHT THAT WAS
SOMETHING EVERY NOBLE HAS.
Tiese: CERTAINLY NOT!
ONLY NOBLES FOURTH RANK OR
HIGHER ARE GRANTED THAT POWER,
WHEREAS NOBLES WHO ARE
RANKED FIFTH AND LOWER
MUST ADHERE TO THE JUDGMENT
OF THOSE OF HIGHER RANKING!
Eugeo: OH. INTERESTING.
Tiese: UH, ANYWAY...
THAT’S WHY SOMEONE LIKE MYSELF,
AN HEIR TO A SIXTH-RANK HOUSE,
IS AN ARISTOCRAT IN NAME ONLY.
IN THAT SENSE, OUR LIFESTYLE
IS REALLY NO DIFFERENT
FROM MOST PEOPLE’S.
Eugeo: OH. REALLY?
Kirito: OKAY,
SO IF YOUR OPPONENT
WANTS TO GET THE DROP ON YOU
FROM ABOVE
WITH A HIGH-NORKIAN
STYLE ATTACK,
THERE’S TWO TYPES OF STRIKES
YOU GOTTA BE READY
TO DEFEND YOURSELF AGAINST.
THEY ARE A STRIKE FROM ABOVE
OR DIAGONALLY TO THE RIGHT.
IF THEY DO ANYTHING ELSE,
THAT MEANS THEY’RE GONNA
SWITCH UP THEIR FOOTING,
SO YOU’LL STILL
HAVE TIME TO BLOCK IT.
( Eugeo chuckles )
MAN, I’M STUFFED!
Tiese: UM, IF IT WOULD BE
ALL RIGHT WITH YOU TWO,
WE’D LIKE TO GET
YOUR THOUGHTS ON SOMETHING.
IT’S ABOUT FRENICA,
OUR ROOMMATE AT THE DORMITORY.
( both sigh )
Ronie: THE ELITE DISCIPLE
WHOM SHE UNFORTUNATELY IS FORCED
TO SERVE UNDER
IS A RATHER CRUDE INDIVIDUAL.
OVER THE PAST FEW DAYS,
HE’S BEEN GIVING HER ORDERS THAT
GO WAY BEYOND INAPPROPRIATE.
Eugeo: HIS RANKING IS NO EXCUSE.
IF HE’S MAKING HER DO THINGS
THAT VIOLATE THE SCHOOL’S RULES,
HE SHOULD BE REPORTED.
Tiese: THAT’S JUST IT.
TECHNICALLY,
THEY’RE NOT VIOLATIONS,
BUT THE DEMANDS HE MAKES OF
A FEMALE STUDENT ARE SO OBSCENE.
Eugeo: YOU DON’T
HAVE TO SAY ANY MORE.
THE PROBLEM IS, THE ONLY WAY
TO CHANGE FRENICA’S MENTOR
IS TO GET THE APPROVAL
OF HER CURRENT ONE.
CAN YOU TELL US HIS NAME?
( Tiese sighs ) YES.
IT’S SECOND SEAT ELITE DISCIPLE,
HUMBERT ZIZEK.
Kirito: I’M NOT SURPRISED.
( both gasp )
Eugeo: A FEW DAYS AGO, I HAD
A SPARRING MATCH WITH HUMBERT
IN THE TRAINING HALL.
WE ENDED IT IN A DRAW.
IN FACT, HE SEEMED
PRETTY UPSET BY THAT.
MY GUESS IS HE’S TAKING
HIS FRUSTRATIONS OUT ON FRENICA.
Ronie: HE’S DOING THIS
OUT OF REVENGE?
HOW COULD HE BE SO CRUEL?
Tiese: I JUST
CAN’T UNDERSTAND IT.
WE LIVE IN A LARGER HOUSE
THAN MOST OTHER CIVILIANS
AND ENJOY
SOME ADDITIONAL PRIVILEGES,
BUT MY FATHER
WOULD ALWAYS REMIND ME
THAT WE SHOULD NEVER
TAKE THOSE THINGS FOR GRANTED.
HE’D SAY WE WERE OBLIGED
TO ENSURE EVERYONE,
NO MATTER THEIR STATION,
COULD LIVE
A HAPPY AND PEACEFUL LIFE.
AND IF WAR BROKE OUT,
IT’S OUR DUTY
TO TAKE UP OUR SWORDS FIRST
AND PROTECT THE WEAK.
AND YET,
BECAUSE OF THE HEARTLESS ORDERS
THAT WERE ISSUED BY A NOBLE,
FRENICA COULDN’T HELP BUT CRY
HERSELF TO SLEEP LAST NIGHT.
IT’S NOT RIGHT. HOW CAN
SOMETHING LIKE THIS BE ALLOWED?
( sighs )
THANK YOU.
Kirito: THERE’S A PHRASE
IN THE SACRED TONGUE
THAT COMES TO MIND,
WHICH--LET’S SEE.
IT’S PRONOUNCED
NOBLESSE OBLIGE, I THINK.
BASICALLY IT MEANS
WHOEVER’S GOT THE POWER
SHOULD USE IT
FOR THE SAKE OF THE VULNERABLE,
JUST LIKE YOUR FATHER SAID.
IT’S A CODE OF HONOR,
AND THAT KIND OF HONOR
IS MORE IMPORTANT
THAN ANY LAW OR CUSTOM.
THERE ARE THINGS
YOU JUST SHOULDN’T DO,
EVEN IF THERE’S
NO LAW AGAINST ’EM.
AT THE SAME TIME, THERE MIGHT
BE STUFF YOU SHOULD DO,
EVEN IF THE LAWS
SAY YOU SHOULDN’T.
Ronie: I THINK I UNDERSTAND
WHAT IT IS YOU’RE SAYING.
IF I’M HEARING YOU CORRECTLY...
THE TABOO INDEX
DOESN’T COVER EVERYTHING.
IN CASES LIKE THIS ONE,
WE HAVE TO USE
OUR OWN PERSONAL SENSE
OF WHAT’S RIGHT
AND WHAT’S WRONG.
INSTEAD OF BLINDLY OBEYING LAWS,
WE NEED TO ASK WHY THEY EXIST
AND IF THEY’RE EVEN HONORABLE.
THAT SELF-REFLECTION
IS MORE IMPORTANT
THAN JUST BLIND FAITH.
Kirito: YUP!
THAT’S EXACTLY RIGHT.
IT’S SUPER IMPORTANT TO LEARN
HOW TO ACT AND THINK
FOR YOURSELF.
THAT’S WORTH MORE
THAN THE BEST SWORD
OR THE FLASHIEST MOVE.
EVEN THOUGH HUMBERT DIDN’T
TECHNICALLY BREAK THE RULES,
WHAT HE DID IS STILL 100% WRONG.
SOMEONE’S GOTTA HOLD HIM
ACCOUNTABLE FOR THAT.
IN THIS CASE, IT LOOKS
LIKE IT’S UP TO US TO.
Eugeo: RIGHT.
WE’LL GO AND SORT THIS OUT.
Raios: WELL, WELL.
TO WHAT DO WE OWE THE PLEASURE
OF THIS VISIT, DISCIPLE EUGEO?
AND ON THE EVENING
OF OUR DAY OF REST, NO LESS.
Eugeo: I’VE COME TO REPORT
A TROUBLING RUMOR.
UNFORTUNATELY,
IT CONCERNS DISCIPLE ZIZEK.
I THOUGHT I’D BRING THIS
TO YOUR ATTENTION
BEFORE IT DAMAGED
HIS STELLAR REPUTATION.
Humbert: ARE YOU MOCKING ME?!
Raios: OH, MY.
I MUST SAY I’M SURPRISED.
I WOULDN’T HAVE
EXPECTED THIS FROM YOU.
HOW THOUGHTFUL OF YOU
TO BE CONCERNED
FOR THE SAKE
OF MY FRIEND’S GOOD NAME.
HOWEVER, I’M AFRAID
I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT THIS RUMOR
YOU SPEAK OF COULD BE.
ALONG WITH THE NATURE
OF THESE CLAIMS,
I MUST ASK WHERE YOU
ACQUIRED THIS INFORMATION.
Eugeo: FROM LORD ZIZEK’S PAGE,
ALONG WITH THE GIRLS
WHO ROOM WITH HER.
AS FAR AS THE CLAIMS
ARE CONCERNED,
THEY SAY LORD ZIZEK
HAS BEEN ISSUING PERVERSE ORDERS
TO HIS PAGE, FRENICA.
Raios: WHAT ARE
THESE "PERVERSE ORDERS"?
I’M NOT FOLLOWING WHAT IT IS
YOU’RE GETTING AT, SIR EUGEO.
WHICH OF THE SCHOOL’S
REGULATIONS
HAS HE VIOLATED SPECIFICALLY?
( Eugeo gasps )
( sighs )
SIR, EVEN IF SOMETHING ISN’T
SPECIFICALLY FORBIDDEN HERE,
DO YOU NOT AGREE THERE ARE
THINGS AN ELITE DISCIPLE
SHOULD NEVER DO
AS A PRIMARY TRAINEE’S MENTOR?
Raios: OH, HO!
I CAN TELL THIS UPSETS YOU.
NOW THEN, WHAT EXACTLY
ARE YOU INSINUATING
HUMBERT FORCED FRENICA TO DO?
Eugeo: I COULDN’T SAY.
Raios: WELL,
WHAT SAY YOU, HUMBERT?
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT IT IS SIR EUGEO
COULD BE REFERRING TO?
Humbert: NOT EVEN THE FOGGIEST!
TRY AS I MIGHT, I CAN’T MAKE
HEADS NOR TAILS OF IT.
IT IS TRUE THAT I ASKED HER
TO PERFORM
SOME MENIAL TASKS FOR ME.
BUT EVER SINCE MY DUEL
WITH SIR EUGEO,
WHICH REGRETTABLY ENDED
IN A DRAW, I’M A CHANGED MAN
AND HAVE IMMERSED MYSELF
FULLY IN MY TRAINING!
WHY, I’VE BEEN USING MUSCLES
I DID NOT KNOW I HAD,
AND, AS A RESULT,
MY BODY ACHED SO BADLY.
IN SUCH A HUMBLED STATE
AS I WAS IN,
I HAD NO CHOICE BUT TO ASK HER
TO MASSAGE ME EVERY NIGHT
WHILE I BATHED.
( Eugeo gasps )
Humbert: I WAS CONCERNED
SHE WOULD SOIL HER UNIFORM,
SO I GRACIOUSLY
HAD HER STRIP DOWN
AND MASSAGE ME
IN HER UNDERGARMENTS.
HONESTLY, I CAN’T
FOR THE LIFE OF ME UNDERSTAND
HOW ANYONE
COULD THINK THAT PERVERSE.
Eugeo: BECAUSE OF YOUR BEHAVIOR,
FRENICA HAS BEEN BESIDE HERSELF.
IF YOU CONTINUE HARASSING HER,
I WILL BE FORCED
TO BRING IT TO THE ATTENTION
OF OUR INSTRUCTORS.
I HOPE YOU UNDERSTAND.
- Humbert: WHY, YOU...
- ( Raios claps )
Raios: I APPRECIATE THE WARNING,
DISCIPLE EUGEO.
DO WHATEVER YOU FEEL IS RIGHT.
( Eugeo grunts )
Kirito: DON’T LET
THOSE JERKS GET TO YOU.
Eugeo: I DON’T KNOW
HOW YOU KEPT SO CALM.
I THOUGHT I WAS GOING
TO LOSE IT IN THERE.
Kirito: LUCKY FOR THEM,
YOU DIDN’T HAVE YOUR SWORD.
WELL, AT LEAST,
NOW I’M PRETTY SURE
THEY’RE UP TO SOMETHING MORE
THAN JUST BEING CREEPS.
- Eugeo: WHAT?
- Kirito: I GET THE FEELING
THE REASON THEY’RE GOING
TO ALL THIS TROUBLE
IS TO SET A TRAP FOR YOU.
Eugeo: REALLY?
Kirito: YEAH. LOOK,
IF YOU’D TAKEN THEIR BAIT AND
STARTED GOING OFF ON HUMBERT,
THEY COULD HAVE ACCUSED YOU
OF BEING DISRESPECTFUL TO THEM,
AND THEY’D BE IN THEIR RIGHTS
TO PUNISH YOU. YOU SEE?
( Eugeo sighs )
( Kirito sighs ) DON’T WORRY.
IF HUMBERT DOESN’T STOP
MESSING WITH FRENICA, HE’LL PAY.
FOR NOW, ALL WE CAN DO
IS TELL THE TEACHERS,
SO STAY SHARP,
AND KEEP YOUR EYES OPEN.
Eugeo: ALL RIGHT. I’LL DO THAT.
Kirito: AND, EUGEO, IF
THOSE GUYS SAY ANYTHING TO YOU
WHEN I’M NOT AROUND,
TRY NOT TO GET YOURSELF
ALL RILED UP
LIKE YOU DID BACK THERE.
Eugeo: I-I WON’T. I PROMISE.
I’LL JUST, YOU KNOW, STAY COOL.
Kirito: EXACTLY.
STAY COOL ALWAYS.
Tiese: ALLOW ME
TO MAKE MY REPORT!
ALL CHORES ARE DONE.
THE ASSIGNED CLEANING
HAS ALSO BEEN COMPLETED.
Eugeo: GOOD WORK, AS USUAL.
I REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
Tiese: OH, IT’S NOTHING!
I’M YOUR PAGE, AFTER ALL.
Eugeo: BY THE WAY,
IF YOU HAVE THE TIME,
I’D LIKE TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT SOMETHING.
YOU DON’T HAVE TO STAND.
PLEASE, SIT DOWN.
( Tiese gasps )
VERY WELL. IF YOU INSIST.
Eugeo: UH...
( clears throat )
IT’S ABOUT FRENICA.
I HAD A TALK WITH HUMBERT
ABOUT HER YESTERDAY.
Tiese: DID YOU, REALLY?!
Eugeo: I DOUBT HE WANTS
TO GET INTO ANY TROUBLE,
SO I’M PRETTY SURE HE WON’T BE
HARASSING HER ANYMORE.
Tiese: THANK GOODNESS.
YOU DON’T KNOW
HOW GRATEFUL I AM,
ELITE DISCIPLE EUGEO, SIR!
Eugeo: YOUR WORK’S
DONE FOR TODAY,
SO PLEASE JUST CALL ME EUGEO.
ANYWAY, THERE’S SOMETHING
I NEED TO APOLOGIZE FOR.
I WASN’T SURE OF IT YESTERDAY,
BUT NOW I AM.
THE REASON THIS HAPPENED
IN THE FIRST PLACE
WAS ALL BECAUSE OF THE DUEL
I HAD WITH HUMBERT.
DO YOU THINK YOU COULD SET UP
A MEETING WITH HER FOR ME?
I’D LIKE TO APOLOGIZE IN PERSON.
( Tiese gasps )
YES. OF COURSE.
HONESTLY, DESPITE WHAT YOU SAY,
NONE OF THIS
IS REALLY YOUR FAULT.
BUT I’LL BE MORE THAN HAPPY
TO CONVEY YOUR WISHES TO HER,
NONE THE LESS.
UM, C-COULD I...
Eugeo: MM?
Tiese: C-COULD I
SIT CLOSER TO YOU?
Eugeo: UH...
SURE.
Tiese: I’VE BEEN THINKING.
AFTER I GRADUATE
FROM THE ACADEMY,
I’LL TAKE OVER AS HEAD
OF THE SCHTRINEN FAMILY.
AS IS CUSTOM, I WILL THEN
HAVE TO MARRY A NOBLE
WHO IS OF THE SAME RANK
OR POSSIBLY HIGHER.
AND IT TERRIFIES ME!
( Eugeo gasps )
Tiese: WHAT IF THE MAN
WHO BECOMES MY HUSBAND
TURNS OUT TO BE
SOMEONE LIKE LORD ZIZEK,
SOMEONE WHO IS CRUEL TO OTHERS
AND WHO LACKS
THE BASIC PRINCIPLES OF HONOR
MY FATHER RAISED ME TO UPHOLD?
I’M SO SCARED.
WHAT DO I DO?
( Eugeo gasps )
♪
TIESE.
Tiese: EUGEO, IF--
IF IT WOULD BE ALL RIGHT,
I’D LIKE TO ASK
ANOTHER FAVOR OF YOU.
I HAVE NO DOUBT THAT EVENTUALLY
YOU’LL RISE
TO THE TOP OF OUR CLASS,
WIN THE SWORDSMANSHIP
TOURNAMENT,
AND COMPETE IN THE FOUR EMPIRE
UNIFICATION TOURNAMENT.
Eugeo: UH, I HOPE TO.
I MEAN, I AM WORKING HARD
TOWARD THAT GOAL.
Tiese: AND THEN,
AFTER THAT, IF YOU--
IF YOU RANK HIGH
IN THE UNIFICATION TOURNAMENT,
I HEARD YOU CAN BE
APPOINTED AS A NOBLE.
THAT’S WHAT HAPPENED WITH
OUR SUPERVISOR, MS. AZURICA.
AND THEN, IF YOU DO
DECIDE TO TAKE A TITLE,
DO YOU THINK--
WOULD YOU BE MY--
♪
Eugeo: I’M NOT HERE
FOR THE TOURNAMENT.
I’M DOING THIS
TO BECOME AN INTEGRITY KNIGHT
AND FIND ALICE,
BUT I CAN’T TELL HER THAT.
( sighs )
IT’S OKAY.
AFTER THE TOURNAMENT,
WE’LL TALK MORE ABOUT THIS.
Tiese: I’LL BE WAITING,
AND I’LL WORK AS HARD AS YOU!
I WANT TO BECOME STRONG ENOUGH
SO THAT I CAN SPEAK UP
FOR WHAT IS RIGHT.
JUST LIKE YOU, EUGEO.
Singer: ♪ THE IRIS TO YOU ♪